<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: G.E.M. Tang | C-Pop Sunday]]></title>
  <link href="http://cpopsunday.github.io/blog/categories/g-dot-e-m-tang/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://cpopsunday.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-04T00:07:56-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://cpopsunday.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[jessica507]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/4/2014 Aka the First Edition of C-Pop Sunday]]></title>
    <link href="http://cpopsunday.github.io/blog/2014/05/03/first-edition-of-c-pop-sunday/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-03T20:29:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://cpopsunday.github.io/blog/2014/05/03/first-edition-of-c-pop-sunday</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to our very own first edition of C-Pop Sunday, where we will list our 3 favorite Chinese Pop tracks of the week and post additional links to their stores or any social media player sites if I can find them! <br /></p>

<br />


<p>First, if you want to see all the videos in one place, click on the playlist! Otherwise, keep reading.
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4Jt4hT47EsGxfSy7pMDiOzvFRS2_rCv6">Playlist</a><iframe width="770" height="433" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?list=PL4Jt4hT47EsGxfSy7pMDiOzvFRS2_rCv6" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>

<br>


<p>Let&rsquo;s get into today&rsquo;s list of hand-selected hot tracks, in no particular order:</p>

<br />




<ul>
<li><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Khalil_Fong">Khalil Fong</a>'s Xiao Fang: Khalil Fong is a talented Hong Kong-based singer-songwriter whose music hints of soul and R&amp;B influences. His song Xiao Fang is currently a chart-topper on the Beijing radio charts so here is a preview of it so you can go check him out on Youtube, iTunes, Spotify, Yesasia!</li>
<iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="433" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebtlgEJvrlI" width="770"></iframe>
<ul>
<li>iTunes: <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/tw/album/wei-xian-shi-jie/id836001442?l=zh%C2%A0">https://itunes.apple.com/tw/album/wei-xian-shi-jie/id836001442?l=zh&nbsp;</a> </li>
<li>Yesasia: <a href="http://www.yesasia.com/global/%E5%8D%B1%E9%9A%AA%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C-%E9%A0%90%E8%B3%BC%E9%99%90%E5%AE%9A%E7%89%88/1035338777-0-0-0-en/info.html">http://www.yesasia.com/global/%E5%8D%B1%E9%9A%AA%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C-%E9%A0%90%E8%B3%BC%E9%99%90%E5%AE%9A%E7%89%88/1035338777-0-0-0-en/info.html</a></li>
</ul>
<li><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jane_Zhang">Jane Zhang Liang Ying</a>'s Wo Shi Wo De or roughly translated to "I Am Mine" has a pretty cool video and catchy tunes that you can't miss this week! After she finished 3rd in a singing competition a few years ago, she has been releasing many singles and winning quite a few awards so it's not strange to see that her new track and video is currently in the top 10 videos in YinYueTai's VChart. Check it out!
</li>
<iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="433" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/35a1-jPNGl0" width="770"></iframe>
<ul>
<li>Could not find any iTunes albums for Jane, but found some other <a href="https://play.spotify.com/artist/4KNEctE2dk3QXwzjCBcZtw">Spotify tracks for her</a> including the amazing "I Believe".</li>
</ul>
<li><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jess_Lee_Kar_Wei">Jess Lee</a>'s Laugh To Tears. Jess Lee is a very talented Malaysian singer and winner of a singing competition in Taiwan where she's currently living. She has released a couple of interesting music videos after the competition, that despite containing some non-PG themes, definitely show that this girl can really sing.<ul><li>iTunes: <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/hk/album/cliff-to-the-heaven/id849487621?i=849487697">https://itunes.apple.com/hk/album/cliff-to-the-heaven/id849487621?i=849487697</a></li></ul>
</li><iframe width="770" height="433" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gzzPrsBOK1E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
<li>Blast-From-The-Past Bonus Song: Seven Sense's Jade Smoke. Seven Sense is a fairly recently-formed group of professional dancers whose music has elements of traditional Chinese instruments and whose music videos include very classy and graceful dances with fans and traditional Chinese dance moves. All the seven members in the group are also very young but experienced in dance so there is definitely lots of potential and I seriously look forward to their future performances. For more information on the group's members, go to <a href="http://onehallyu.com/index.php?/topic/9410-the-official-seven-sense-%E4%B8%83%E6%9C%B5%E7%BB%84%E5%90%88-thread/">OneHallyu</a>. For today's blast from the past song, we have this song which was one of their first singles released last year. Enjoy! </li>
<iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="433" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/hRjQUVHsYbg" width="770"></iframe>
</ul>


<br>


<p>That is it for this week&rsquo;s short and sweet list of noteworthy music videos and songs in Chinese Pop!</p>

<br>


<p>Feel free to send over song recommendations that may appear on the next episode of C-Pop Sunday!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
